# Vedran Arnautovic

Senior Product Designer, Zendesk

527 Brunswick Street Fitzroy North VIC 3068

phone 0434 490 076 web vedran.io email hello@vedran.io twitter @vedranio

I'm a user centred designer equally comfortable in the minutiae of pixel detail and ambiguity of early product discovery. I focus on UX design, usability, interaction design and user research. I can code (a little).

I get a kick out of working with passionate teams, seeing people interact with the products I design, and making those interactions more intuitive and useful.

# Experience

#### Zendesk

Nov 2017 – present

#### **SEEK**

Jan 2014 - Nov 2017

#### **Senior Product Designer**

### Senior UX Designer

I've led design on key initiatives within SEEK, spanning both sides of the marketplace.

My work was a mixture of tactical projects working closely with agile teams, and more strategic efforts working with senior leaders to define the future of SEEK's products.

## **Freelance**

Sep 2016 - Oct 2017

## Lead UX designer

#### **Gymsales**

Lead all aspects of design for Gymsales.

#### Rubicon

Ran a design sprint for Rubicon's clients and created a prototype for the solution we designed.

#### **Kolektiv**

Over 6 months, I coached Kolektiv's product team on usability testing and lean UX practices.

#### **SMS**

Sep 2010 - Jan 2014

## Consultant (UX designer and BA)

- UX Designer and BA (NAB)
- UX Designer (NAB)
- Interface Designer and BA (BP)

Internally, I was appointed the Customer Experience (CX) lead for Victoria kickstarted the development of our CX capability.

## Leica

Feb 2009 – Sep 2010 Melbourne

#### System Design Engineer & BA

Upon returning to Melbourne, I worked with Leica's software team to define design improvements based on my field research.

#### Leica

Feb 2007 - Feb 2009 London

## **System Design Engineer**

A career shaping opportunity allowed me to spend two years researching how our clients and support teams interacted with our instruments, and to use those findings to design better solutions for them.

## **Vision BioSystems**

Jan 2004 - Feb 2007

## Software Engineer

I started out very technical, developing software for medical devices. Working in an organisation with no designers created a window of opportunity to start designing and show initiative to test software with users.

# Education

#### Univ. of Melbourne

1999 - 2004

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Bachelor's degree, Mechatronics

# Tools

Sketch, Adobe CC, Marvel, Invision, Axure, Morae, Principle, Framer.js, CSS, HTML, Javascript, Github

+ anything else I need to learn.